<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Convert temperature to Fahrenheit</string>
    <string name="app_about">There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin, and according to the International System of Units, the kelvin unit was adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but The United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure temperature, and there are differences between these units, as they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius) and Fahrenheit And kelvin), and according to the International System of Units, the kelvin unit was adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure the temperature, and there are differences between these units as they are not They are equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures (degrees Celsius (Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin), and according to the system states J for units The kelvin unit has been adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure the temperature, and there are differences between these units as they are not equal, and therefore there are laws that use To convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit and Kelvin, and according to the International System of Units the kelvin unit has been adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, i.e. Degrees Celsius to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure temperature, and there are differences between these units, they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. The temperature is (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin), and according to the International System of Units, the kelvin unit is adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure Temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure temperature, and there are differences between these units, they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. Degrees Celsius (Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin), and according to the International System of Units, the kelvin unit is adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure temperature There are differences between these units as they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin, and according to the international system of units has been adopted. The kelvin unit to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure the temperature, and it is There are differences between these units, they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin, and according to the international system of units has been adopted The kelvin unit to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure the temperature, and there are differences between these units, as they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units Here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin, and according to the International System of Units the kelvin unit is adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius. Heat because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure the temperature, and there are differences between these units, they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention We will explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin, and according to the International System of Units, the kelvin unit is adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because Easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure temperature, and there are differences between these units, they are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures are (degrees Celsius) Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin), and according to the International System of Units, the kelvin unit was adopted to measure the temperature, but it is common to use the Celsius system, meaning degrees Celsius, to measure the temperature because it is easy and simple, but the United States of America uses the Fahrenheit system to measure the temperature, and there are differences between These units are not equal, and therefore there are laws used to convert between these units, and here we will mention and explain some of them. There are three units used in measuring temperatures: (degrees Celsius), Fahrenheit, and Kelvin, and sense</string>
    <string name="calculate_button">Calculate the temperature in Fahrenheit</string>
</resources>